<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="copyright_content">"\"APPLICATION AGREEMENT AND TERMS OF USE  1. Introduction THE APPLICATION AND RELATED CONTENT AND SERVICES ARE PROVIDED SUBJECT TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING INFORMATION CAREFULLY. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE APPLICATION WILL INDICATE YOUR AGREEMENT TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, PROMPTLY EXIT THE APPLICATION. IMPORTANT NOTICE TO YOU These Terms and Conditions of Use and the Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Terms and Conditions”), govern your use of the application, including without limitation use of all content, data, images, information and other materials posted on or available through the application (collectively, the “Application”). By using the Application, you agree that you have reviewed and understood these Terms and Conditions of Use and the Privacy Policy to your full satisfaction, that you accept and are subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use and the Privacy Policy, and that iHealth Labs, Inc. (“iHealth”) is permitted to use the information it collects through the Application as set forth below or in the Privacy Policy. If you are not in agreement with the Terms and Conditions, you must immediately leave and no longer use the Application. To the extent that there is any conflict between a provision of the Terms and Conditions of Use and a provision in this Privacy Policy, the provision in the Terms and Conditions of Use shall prevail. If you breach any of these Terms and Conditions, your authorization to use the Application shall automatically terminate. These Terms and Conditions are in addition to any other agreement you may have with iHealth, including any agreement governing purchase or use of iHealth’s products or services by you or your organization.  2. Ownership The Application is owned and operated by iHealth. Except for Third Party Content (defined below) all content, data, information and other materials on or directly accessible from the Application, is owned by iHealth, its affiliates, licensors and/or vendors. The Application and all content is protected by United States and international copyright and trademark laws. Any rights not expressly granted by these Terms and Conditions or any applicable end user license agreements are reserved by iHealth and/or its vendors and licensors.  Except for Third Party Content, the contents of the Application may not be distributed, modified, reproduced, or used, in whole or in part, without the prior written consent of iHealth, except that you may download content from the Application to any single computer, provided you keep intact all copyright, trademark, and other proprietary notices and comply with these terms and any additional applicable end user license agreements. Except as provided in these Terms and Conditions, any use of these materials on any other Application or networked computer environment for any purpose is prohibited.  3. Third Party Content The Application may display, include, make available, or otherwise link to content, data, information, applications, web Applications, or other materials generated or provided by third parties (“Third Party Content”). You understand that Third Party Content may include content that may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable, or that may be inaccurate, unresponsive, unreliable, or even untruthful. By using the Application, you acknowledge and agree that iHealth shall not be responsible for examining or evaluating the content, accuracy, completeness, timeliness, validity, copyright compliance, legality, decency, quality or any other aspect of Third Party Content. iHealth does not warrant or endorse and does not assume and will not have any liability or responsibility to you or any other person for any Third Party Content. Third Party Content is provided “AS IS” and solely as a convenience to you, with no warranties of any kind.  You agree that iHealth shall not be liable or otherwise responsible for any content or information you post in a web-forum, in a chat room, or through other interactive or “social networking” portions of the Application (your “Personal Content”) and that such Personal Content may be immediately displayed on the Application and treated as Third Party Content. The generation and distribution of Personal Content is at your own risk. You further agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless iHealth and its affiliates and their customers, suppliers, employees, officers, directors, and agents from and against any and all claims, losses, liabilities, suits, costs, and other damages arising out of or related to your Personal Content, including claims that the Personal Content violates, infringes, or misappropriates the patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright, or other proprietary rights of any party; that the Personal Content is libelous or defamatory; or that the Personal Content caused or attributed to the injury or death to a third party. You hereby grant to iHealth and its suppliers a non-exclusive, transferable, worldwide, royalty free, sublicensable, right and license to store, copy, distribute, transmit, publicly perform, display, create derivative works of, and otherwise use the Personal Content for purposes of providing the Application to third parties, including the right to transmit the Personal Content to other users of the Application. 4. iHealth Does Not Provide Medical Advice The contents of the Application are not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. iHealth does not recommend or endorse any specific tests, products, procedures, opinions or other information mentioned on the Application. 5. No Framing You may not frame or utilize framing techniques to use, surround or enclose any of iHealth’s names, trademarks, service marks, logos, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) of iHealth and/or its affiliates without IHealth’s express written consent.  6. Jurisdiction The Application is controlled and operated by iHealth from its offices within the State of California, United States of America. iHealth makes no representation that materials in the Application are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access the Application from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local or national laws, if and to the extent local or national laws are applicable. The software, technology and other information from the Application is further subject to United States export controls and, potentially, the import laws of your jurisdiction. No software, technology or other information from the Application may be downloaded or otherwise exported or re-exported to any person or entity on the U.S. Treasury Department's list of Specially Designated Nationals or the U.S. Commerce Department's Table of Denial Orders or otherwise prohibited by United States export control laws. By downloading or otherwise using any software, technology or other information from the Application in any manner whatsoever, you represent and warrant that you are not on any such list or located in, under the control of, or a national or resident of any such country. 7. Trademarks “IHEALTH” “IHEALTH.COM” and related designs are trademark(s) and service mark(s) owned by iHealth. iHealth’s trademarks and service marks may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not from iHealth, in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers, or in any manner that disparages or discredits iHealth.  8. iHealth’s Use of Your Data and Communications Except as expressly provided in iHealth’s Privacy Policy, you acknowledge that any Personal Content, communications, material, information, or data of any kind that you e-mail, post, or transmit to or through the Application, including, questions, comments, suggestions and other information (your “Communications”) will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary by iHealth. You hereby represent and warrant that you have the right to provide to iHealth all Communications you submit to iHealth through the Application.  YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT SECURITY SAFEGUARDS, BY THEIR NATURE, ARE CAPABLE OF CIRCUMVENTION AND IHEALTH DOES NOT AND CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT YOUR INFORMATION OR COMMUNICATIONS CANNOT BE ACCESSED BY UNAUTHORIZED PERSONS CAPABLE OF OVERCOMING SUCH SAFEGUARDS. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT: (I) VIRUSES, WORMS, TROJAN HORSES, OR OTHER UNDESIRABLE DATA OR SOFTWARE; OR (II) UNAUTHORIZED USERS (e.g., HACKERS) MAY ATTEMPT TO OBTAIN ACCESS TO AND DAMAGE THE APPLICATION, YOUR INFORMATION OR COMMUNICATIONS, AND/OR IHEALTH’S NETWORKS. IHEALTH SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR SUCH ACTIVITIES OR FOR YOUR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE THE APPLICATION. YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR THE SECURITY AND INTEGRITY OF YOUR INFORMATION AND SYSTEMS. 9. Hyperlinking to the Application Except as specifically provided in these Terms and Conditions, you may not create hyperlinks to the Application. You may provide hyperlinks to the Application on a non-commercial, not-for-profit Application, freely accessible by the public at no charge, provided that “deep links” (e.g., hyperlinks other than to iHealth’s homepage currently located at www.IHealth.com) must be in accordance with any additional terms, conditions and/or technical instructions that iHealth may post on the Application from time-to-time. If you desire to link to the Application in any other manner, you must obtain iHealth’s written permission pursuant to a Hyperlink Agreement. You shall not link to the Application in any manner which states or implies any affiliation between you or your organization and iHealth, or any sponsorship, approval or recommendation of you or your organization by iHealth. Any permitted link to the Application must clearly identify iHealth as the owner of the Application. iHealth reserves the right to redirect any links to the Application to any page it chooses.  10. Acceptable Use As a condition of your use of the Application, you warrant to iHealth that you will not (i) use the Application for any purpose that is unlawful, (ii) use the Application for any commercial purpose, (iii) modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, or distribute the Application in any manner, (iv) use or exploit the Application in an abusive, improper, or illegal manner as determined solely by iHealth, including but not limited to, by trespass, burdening network capacity, or using the Application to harass, abuse, stalk, threaten, defame or otherwise infringe or violate the rights of any other party or to transmit illegal, pornographic, libelous, profane or otherwise offensive messages or content, (v) create derivative works based on the Application or reverse engineer, deconstruct, disassemble or decompile any software or technology underlying the Application or provided through the Application.  11. External Hyperlinks from the Application The Application may contain hyperlinks to third party Applications. External hyperlinks to or from the Application do not constitute any endorsement or recommendation by iHealth of any third party or its Application, products, resources or other information. An external hyperlink to a Application does not imply that iHealth is affiliated with or sponsors the third party's Application. iHealth is not responsible for any software, data or other information available from any third party Application. You are solely responsible for complying with all terms and conditions of use for the third party Applications. You acknowledge that iHealth shall have no liability for any damage or loss arising from your access to, use of or reliance on any third party Application, software, data, or other information.  12. Accuracy and Integrity of Information Although iHealth attempts to ensure the integrity and accuracy of the Application, it makes no guarantees whatsoever as to the correctness or accuracy of the Application. It is possible the Application may include typographical errors, inaccuracies or other errors, and that unauthorized additions, deletions and alterations could be made to the Application by third parties. In the event that an inaccuracy arises, please inform iHealth so that it can be corrected. Information contained on the Application, including these Terms and Conditions and the Privacy Policy, may be changed or updated without notice. 13. No Warranty THE APPLICATION AND ALL INFORMATION AND CONTENT AVAILABLE THROUGH THE APPLICATION ARE PROVIDED “AS IS,” WITH ALL FAULTS, AND “AS AVAILABLE”. IHEALTH DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE APPLICATION WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, OR THAT THE RESULTS OF ANY QUERY WILL BE COMPLETE OR ACCURATE. IHEALTH DOES NOT WARRANT THAT ACCESS TO THE APPLICATION WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, OR THAT DEFECTS IN THE APPLICATION WILL BE CORRECTED. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, IHEALTH DOES NOT REPRESENT OR ENDORSE THE ACCURACY OR RELIABILITY OF ANY DATA, DESCRIPTION, IDENTIFICATION OR OTHER INFORMATION DISPLAYED, DISTRIBUTED, HYPERLINKED OR OTHERWISE REFERRED TO THROUGH THE APPLICATION. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY LAW, IHEALTH DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, CONFORMITY TO ANY REPRESENTATION OR DESCRIPTION, MERCHANTABILITY, QUALITY OF INFORMATION, QUIET ENJOYMENT, AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. 14. Limitation of Liability NEITHER IHEALTH NOR ITS AFFILIATES, NOR THEIR LICENSORS OR SUPPLIERS, WILL BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE, OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES OR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA, OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF (OR INABILITY TO USE) THE APPLICATION OR THE INFORMATION CONTAINED THEREIN, HOWEVER ARISING, EVEN IF IHEALTH OR ITS AFFILIATES OR THEIR REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THIS LIMITATION DOES NOT APPLY TO THE EXTENT IT IS PROHIBITED BY LAW. YOUR SOLE REMEDY FOR DISSATISFACTION WITH THE APPLICATION OR OTHER APPLICATION-RELATED CONTENT, INFORMATION, SERVICES, AND/OR HYPERLINKED APPLICATIONS IS TO STOP USING THE APPLICATION AND/OR SUCH CONTENT, INFORMATION, SERVICES, OR SERVICES. CERTAIN STATE LAWS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES. IF THESE LAWS APPLY TO YOU, SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS, OR LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, AND YOU MIGHT HAVE ADDITIONAL RIGHTS. 15. Indemnification You agree to indemnify and defend iHealth and its affiliates, and their respective officers, directors, shareholders, employees, and agents from any claims, actions, losses, liabilities, damages, costs, and expenses (including attorneys fees and costs) directly or indirectly arising from your (a) use of the Application, (b) violation of any third party right, or (c) breach of any of these Terms and Conditions. You agree to cooperate as fully as reasonably required in the defense of any claim. iHealth reserves the right, at its own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification under this section and, in any event, you agree not to settle any such matter without the prior written consent of iHealth. 16. Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement iHealth respects the intellectual property of others. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide iHealth the following information:  1. An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest; 2. A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;  3. A description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the Application; 4. Your address, telephone number, and email address;  5. A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; 6. A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner's behalf. 17. Changes to these Terms and Conditions iHealth reserves the right to make changes to these Terms and Conditions, including the Privacy Policy, at any time. Please check these Terms and Conditions and the Privacy Policy when you use the Application to ensure that you are aware of any changes. The Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy will indicate the date they were last updated. Your continued use of the Application, including use after the posting of any changes to these terms, will be deemed acceptance by you of the then-current Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy.  18. General Except as provided below, the Terms and Conditions constitute the entire agreement between iHealth and you pertaining to the subject matter hereof. Certain provisions of these Terms and Conditions may be superseded by expressly designated legal notices or terms located on particular pages within the Application. The parties agree that any and all disputes, claims or controversies arising out of or relating to these Terms and Conditions that are not resolved by mutual agreement shall be governed by California law, without giving effect to principles of conflicts of laws provisions thereof, and submitted to final and binding arbitration before JAMS, or its successor, pursuant to the United States Arbitration Act, 9 U.S.C. Sec. 1 et seq. The arbitration shall take place in San Francisco, California unless the parties otherwise agree in writing. Within fourteen (14) days thereafter, the arbitrator shall arrive at a final decision, which shall be reduced to writing, signed by the arbitrator, and mailed to each of the parties and their legal counsel. All decisions of the arbitrator shall be final, binding and conclusive on the parties and shall constitute the only method of resolving disputes or matters subject to arbitration pursuant to this Agreement; provided, however, nothing shall prohibit the parties from seeking injunctive relief and/or other equitable remedies in a court of competent jurisdiction. The arbitrator or a court of appropriate jurisdiction may issue a writ of execution to enforce the arbitrator's judgment. Judgment may be entered upon such a decision in accordance with applicable law in any court having jurisdiction thereof. 19. Additional Android Device Terms This Section 19 applies to you only if you use the Application on an Android device (e.g., iPhone, iPad, iPod Touch) (any such device, an 'Android Device'); Section 19 does not apply to you if you do not use the Application on an Android Device. We are solely responsible for the Application on your Android Device, and you may use the Application on your Android Device only as permitted by these Terms of Use and the 'Usage Rules' set forth in the Application Store Terms and Conditions (http://www.Android.com/legal/itunes/appstore/us/terms.html). As between iHealth and Android Inc., to the extent that: (a) we are required to address any claims related to your or a third party's use or possession of the Application on your Android Device, we will be responsible for addressing, investigating, or defending the claim; and (b) we have not effectively disclaimed any warranties relating to the Application on your Android Device, we will be solely responsible for any product warranties or other claims, losses, liabilities, damages, costs or expenses if the Application fails to conform to any warranty. If the Application on your Android Device fails to conform to any applicable warranty, you may notify Android Inc. for a refund of the purchase price of the Application on your Android Device, if any. Android Inc. will not have any other warranty obligations whatsoever with respect to the Application on your Android Device. Android Inc. and its subsidiaries are third party beneficiaries to these Terms of Use and that upon your acceptance of these Terms of Use, Android Inc. and its subsidiaries may enforce these Terms of Use against you as a third party beneficiary of these Terms of Use.  If you have any questions concerning these Terms and Conditions, or you desire to contact iHealth for any reason, please write:   719 N. Shoreline Blvd. Mountain View, CA 94043 support@ihealthlabs.com\" "</string>
</resources>