<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--*********************************** am3s 所有***********************************  -->


    <!-- *********************************** am4 所有faq  ***********************************-->
    <!-- Product Information -->  
    <string name="astfaq_am4_1">1. What is the iHealth Wave?</string> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_2">2. How to detect swim?</string> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_3">3. Which data will be recorded?</string> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_4">4. How to ware the Wave?</string> 

    <!--Swim Mode--> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_5">1.How many swimming styles can be detected?</string> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_6">2.Is there any attention when you swim?</string> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_7">3.How long the swimming summary will be displayed?</string> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_8">4.What data will be displayed when swimming?</string> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_9">5.What data will be displayed when fininshed swim?</string> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_10">6.How to exit swim mode?</string> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_11">7.Can I take shower with the Wave?</string> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_12">
        8.Can I turn off the swim mode if I don\'t need it,and how to turn off?</string> 
    <string name="astfaq_am4_13">9.Can I wear Wave with the clip when swimming?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_14">6.In the process of swimming Wave did not enter into the swimming mode</string>

    <!-- Set Up -->
    <string name="astfaq_am4_15">1. First time using iHealth Wave</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_16">2. How do I set up my iHealth Wave on my device?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_17">3. Why do I need to “link” the Tracker to my iHealth MyVitals account?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_18">4. Can I link the iHealth Wave to multiple accounts?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_19">5. What if I want to give my Tracker to someone else?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_20">6. Why should I update my Android App?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_21">7. When does my iHealth Wave reset and what happens to the previous data?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_22">8. Does the iHealth wave have PC connectivity?</string>


    <!-- Activity Tracking -->

    <string name="astfaq_am4_23">1. How does calorie-tracking work?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_24">2. Is the iHealth Wave suitable for all physical activities?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_25">3. What is workout mode?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_26">4. How much data can the tracker store?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_27">5. How water resistant is iHealth wave?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_28">6. How do I switch mode?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_29">7. How to turn off the alarms?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_30">8. How does the Idle Alarm work and how do I set it up?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_31">9. How does the Activity Level feature work?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_32">9. Can I wear the iHealth wave while performing rigorous activities such as basketball, soccer and other team sports?</string>

    <!-- Charging And Battery -->


    <!-- <string name="astfaq_am3s_28">28. How do I charge the Activity Tracker?</string> -->

    <string name="astfaq_am4_33">1. Can I check the battery level on the Tracker?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_34">2. How long does the battery last on a full charge?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_35">3. Tips to charging</string>

    <!-- Syncing Your iHealth Wave -->

    <string name="astfaq_am4_36">1. How does the iHealth wave sync with the iHealth MyVitals App?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_37">2. How often should I sync Tracker data with my Android device?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_38">3. Does the Tracker need to be near the Android device for syncing?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_39">4. How do I sync the time on the Tracker display when changing time zones?</string>

    <!-- Trouble Shooting -->
    <string name="astfaq_am4_40">1. How do I get iHealth wave firmware updates?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_41">2. How does Reset work?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_42">3. When do I need to reset the iHealth wave and how do I do that?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_43">4. I cannot link my activity tracker with my device.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_44">5. If you are still having trouble syncing your tracker with your device, follow the steps below:</string>


    <!-- am4  faq 在am的基础上添加了几条内容 -->
    <string name="am4s_syncing_your_ihealth_wave">Syncing Your iHealth Wave</string>


    <!--AM4 answer-->
    <!-- product_information-->
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_1">The iHealth Wave analyses and record the number of steps, distance travelled, calories burned, swimming data, and sleep efficiency. Its silent alarm will wake you up gently without waking the person next to you, and its alarm will remind you to be more active. Wave has great water resistance ability, support swimming activity, records and displays swimming styles, duration for each style, calories burned, total duration, total strokes, and strokes per minute. It connects to all smartphones that support Bluetooth 4.0.</string>
     
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_2">Wave uses a 3-axis accelerometer to analyze your movements, when you swim, it can detect correctly, and auto switch to swim mode. Swim mode count one lap as unit to record data. If you have one style during one lap, Wave record the only styles, but if you have more than two styles during one lap, Wave will do analysis which is the biggest styles of the one lap, then all the data will be recorded to the biggest styles of one lap.</string>
     
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_3">Wave can detect swimming style, total swimming duration, duration for each style, swimming stokes, strokes per minutes, and calorie burned.</string>
     
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_4">If you ware it for step trcaking or sleep tracking, you can ware it on your wrist or use the clip, but if you want to swim, you\'d better ware it on your wrist.</string>
     


    <!--Swim Mode-->  
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_5">"Wave can detect 3 different kinds of swimming styles automatically when you swim. Breaststroke Backstroke Freestyle If you swim with other styles, such as butterfly, Wave will count it as swimming, but won’t show butterfly, just showed “unrecognized”, and belong to “other” in the app."</string>
     

    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_6">"1. Water temperature can not  be more than 30°. 2. For resistance the drag of swimming, please wear the Wave close to your wrist. 3. Swimming mode can be set by yourself, if you don\'t need it, turn it off in the app. 4. Swimming mode will increase battery consumption, the usage time would be reduced from 7 days to 5 days. "</string>
     


    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_7">When you swimming in the pool, the summary will be displayed all the time, Wave will show the Time, Swimming Style, and Duration for each style. If you finished swimming and go out of the pool more than 50 steps, the Wave will change to activity mode from swim mode, the total swimming summary will displayed, include Duration, Calories, STR(Strokes), SPM(Strokes per minute). All of the data will displayed behind the objective about 30 minutes, and upload on you app when you connect your device.</string>
     

    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_8">During swimming, Wave will show the Time, Swimming Style, and Duration to users. If you swim more than one style, you need rotate wrist to change displays.</string>
     
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_9">When finished swim, Wave will shows total summary after vibration twice, include Duration, Calories, STR(Strokes), SPM(Strokes per minute). And these date will displayed behind the objective about 30 minutes.</string>
     

    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_10">When you finished swimming, and walked more than 50 steps, Wave will change to activity mode. If Wave still in swim mode, you put it aside, about 30 minutes, it will change to activity mode automatically.</string>
     

    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_11">Yes. You can wear it when you take shower, but water temperature can not be more than 30 degrees. </string>
     

    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_12">Yes, you can turn it off in the app. Make sure your Wave was connected. Open the APP, “Set up my devices-Wave-Swim mode, turn it off.</string>
     

    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_13">No, when swimming, wear Wave on your wrist only, and as close as you can.</string>
      


    <!-- Set Up -->

    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_27">When you first get your tracker, you should fully charge it (about 2~4 hours). To charge, connect the USB end of the charger to your PC and the magnetic end to your tracker. Align and attach the magnetic dots from the charger to the tracker. </string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_28">To protect your personal data, iHealth tracker links the Tracker with your iHealth MyVitals account during your first setup process.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_29">You can only have one Tracker linked to one iHealth MyVitals account at a time.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_30">​A newer version App will contain more features and improvements. Update your App for better performance and bug fixes.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_31">Your Tracker will reset each night at midnight, and all of your data will reset to zero. Your minute-to-minute data will be stored in your Tracker for up to 14 days without syncing. Daily syncing is recommended.</string>







    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_15">Make sure your iHealth Wave is fully charged before pairing. To pair, follow below steps:\n

       a. Download “iHealth MyVitals 2.0” from App Store or Google Play. \n

       b. In your device’s “Settings”, turn the Bluetooth “On”. \n

       c. Open the app and create an iHealth account if you don’t have one. Log in to your account. \n

       d. Bring your tracker close to your device. Click on the menu icon on the top left corner and select “Activity and Sleep”.\n

       e. Click on “Add devices” and select “AM3S” from the device list. Press “Done.”\n

       f. 6 digit numbers will show on your tracker. Enter the last two digits into your mobile device to pair.\n
       g. If you do not see the 6 digits, shut down the app and follow the above steps again. To shut down the running apps in the background, double click on the Home button and swipe up to shut down Apps (android) or hold down your home button and swipe either right or left to shut down Apps (Android).</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_16">Please refer to the “How do I set up my iHealth Wave on my device” and follow the steps to re-link it to another account. Please note that after linking to another account, the data that hasn’t been synced to the original account will be deleted.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_17">Currently, the iHealth Wave has only select android and Android connectivity.</string>

    <!-- Sleep Tracking -->
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_32">Sleep mode will automatically be enabled within 30 minutes of minimal movement. If constant movement occurs, the tracker will reset and the user will have to wait for the allotted time until the sleep mode is achieved.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_33">When you wear the iHealth Activity and Sleep Tracker on your wrist at bedtime, the Tracker will detect and analyze your motion patterns throughout the night, and turn these data into useful information, such as how long it took you to fall asleep, the number of times you woke up throughout the night, and how long you were actually asleep versus merely lying in bed.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_34">Sleep alarms can be set up in the App. Sleep alarms wake you gently—and without disturbing your partner—by vibrating softly for a duration of 40 seconds.</string>


    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_18">The iHealth Wave detects your body movements while you are asleep, such as tossing and turning, then converts that data into Awaken Times. Knowing your total Awaken Times can help you better understand the quality of rest that you are getting.</string>

    <!-- Activity Tracking -->

    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_35">When you walk or run continuously for more than 10 minutes, tracker will generate a summary report with step, distance, calories, and duration information 5 minutes after completing workout.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_36">The tracker can store up to 14 days of data. Data over 14 days old will be replaced automatically by new data.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_37">It is rain, splash and sweat proof. However, it is not waterproof and should not be worn while swimming and showering.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_38">You can lift your wrist and tap to switch to different modes.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_39">When the alarm goes off, shake your tracker to turn it off.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_40">       You can set up the Active Alarm in the iHealth MyVitals App. The Tracker will vibrate gently for approximately 4 seconds to remind you to get up and be more active.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_41">It is safe to wear the Tracker during these rigorous activities, and the Tracker will record your step count from these movements.

        However, the calorie count may not accurately reflect the intensity level of activity performed.</string>


    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_19">The iHealth Wave records calories burned from your activities throughout the day, and your Basal Metabolic Rate (BMR), which is the amount of calories burned while at rest (in other words, the energy expended to sustain your regular body functions while you sleep). This calculation is based on your age, gender, height and weight. The Tracker displays the total calories you have burned since midnight each day.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_20">The Tracker works best when the wrist is moving as part of the overall movement, and your foot makes contact with the ground, such as when walking or running. The iHealth Wave is less suited for tracking resistance exercises such as weight lifting and yoga. Though it will capture data if worn during these activities, these types of motions are not recorded as accurately as running or walking.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_21">To help you stay motivated, the iHealth Wave rewards you at different levels of activity achievement, as indicated by a playful leaping frog who can move to 3rd, 2nd, and 1st place, respectively. This is how it works:

At 2,500 steps: The little guy jumps to 3rd place;"/n"

At 5,000 steps: The little guy jumps to 2nd place;"/n"

At 10,000 steps: The little guy jumps into 1st place and is crowned.</string>

    <!-- Charging And Battery -->
    <!-- Charging And Battery -->

    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_42">The Tracker’s battery level appears on the Tracker display and in the App. When the battery level reaches 20%, the Tracker will vibrate to remind you to recharge it. </string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_43"> \t a. Remove charger from your computer or power outlet to avoid the magnetic connector connects to other objects and become shorted.

b. Charge your tracker when it reaches 20% to optimize battery life.\n</string>


    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_22">The iHealth Wave is powered by a rechargeable built-in battery. The battery typically lasts at 5-7 days between charges depending on the usage. If you check stats frequently or set up multiple alarms, you may need to charge the battery more often.</string>

    <!-- Syncing Your iHealth Wave -->

    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_44">To sync data from your Tracker to the App, you must have Bluetooth turned on.  Launch the App to initiate Bluetooth connection. (On android devices, you should see the Bluetooth icon on the upper-right corner of your android device screen, next to the battery level, flash a few seconds and then stay lit up. This indicates that your iHealth Wave and android device are connected.)

Go to the Activity and Sleep page and then tap on ”sync”. Your tracker should initiate a sync automatically from there.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_45">During syncing, keep the Tracker within 16 feet of your mobile device.</string>


    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_23">A daily sync is recommended but not required. The iHealth Wave can record detailed data for up to 14 days between each sync. Daily syncing only takes a few minutes; however, the more data stored, the longer it may take to sync.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_24">When you travel to a different time zone, the iHealth Wave will automatically update its time when you sync the Tracker with your mobile device.</string>

    <!-- Trouble Shooting -->


    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_46">Reset erases all your personal data from the Tracker, including any un-synced data. Please be sure to sync the Tracker by opening the App before performing a Factory Reset. You will not lose previously synced data in the App and the cloud.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_47">Make sure you meet the following requirements:\n

1.	Make sure you have a supported device. To see the latest list, go to www.ihealthlabs.com/support page.\n

2.	Make sure you are using MyVitals 2.0 and above.\n
3.	Bluetooth is enabled in your android or Android setting.\n </string>
    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_48">        1.	On your android device, double click on the Home button and swipe up to shut down Apps or on Android device, hold down your home button (or press the menu button) and swipe either right or left to shut down Apps.\n

3.	Bluetooth is enabled in your iOS or Android setting.\n

2.	Go to your Bluetooth settings and turn Bluetooth off.\n

3.	Reboot your device.\n

4.	After the reboot cycle has completed, proceed to enable Bluetooth.  Launch the iHealth App and follow the first time setup procedure.\n</string>

     <string name="astfaq_am4_content_14">Make sure your swim mode was opened in the app.\n Please wear it on your wrist and tightly \n
        Your swimming style should keep standard, your action was very important \n
        If cannot get in, please contact our customer services.</string>


    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_25">We are constantly looking for ways to improve your iHealth Wave experience. From time to time, we update the device firmware to enhance product performance. When a firmware update is released, a notification message will pop up in the App. Follow the onscreen instructions to complete the update.</string>

    <string name="astfaq_am4_content_26">If you are experiencing Bluetooth connection difficulties or unusual behavior on the iHealth Wave display, you can perform a basic restart on the tracker to reboot it. Restarting the Tracker will not affect your settings, such as alarms. To reset, connect your Tracker to a powered charger. Hold the button on the side of the charger for ~8 seconds until the tracker displays “Restart complete.”</string>

<!--===============================================-->
    <!-- Blood Pressure Knowledge -->

    <string name="bpfaq_1" translatable="false">1.What is blood pressure?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_2" translatable="false">2.What do the terms “systolic” and “diastolic” mean?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_3" translatable="false">3.What is normal blood pressure?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_4" translatable="false">4.What is high blood pressure / hypertension?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_5" translatable="false">5.How do I know if I have high blood pressure?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_6" translatable="false">6.Should I consult my healthcare provider about my blood pressure readings?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_7" translatable="false">7.How can I understand and interpret my measurement results?</string>

    <!-- ****Before Use -->

    <string name="bpfaq_8" translatable="false">1.How accurate is the iHealth Blood Pressure Monitor Suite of Products?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_9" translatable="false">2.Are there any risks in taking my blood pressure at home with the iHealth Blood Pressure Monitor?</string>

    <!-- ****Use and Tips -->

    <string name="bpfaq_10" translatable="false">1.Can measurements be taken without using a mobile device?</string>

    <!-- ****Data Syncing -->

    <string name="bpfaq_11" translatable="false">1.Can data be shared?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_12" translatable="false">2.How does data upload to my iHealth Cloud Account?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_13" translatable="false">3.Does the App recognize the offline measurement data of multiple users and sort the data automatically?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_14" translatable="false">4.Are there different sizes of cuffs?</string>

    <!-- ****Troubleshooting -->

    <string name="bpfaq_15" translatable="false">1.Why can’t the data be seen on the iHealth Cloud website?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_16" translatable="false">2.Why does the iHealth Blood Pressure Monitor not power on when I apply the cuff?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_17" translatable="false">3.Why does the Bluetooth connection fail?</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_18" translatable="false">4.Why is the “START/STOP” button not working?</string>

    <!-- ****Warranty -->

    <string name="bpfaq_19" translatable="false">1.What are the terms and conditions of the warranty?</string>
    <!-- ****BP totorial-->
    <string name="bpfaq_20" translatable="false">BP3/Ease</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_21" translatable="false">BP5</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_22" translatable="false">BP7</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_23">View</string>

    <!-- content -->

    <string name="bpfaq_content_1">Blood pressure is the force or pressure that is exerted by blood pushing against the walls of the blood vessels throughout the body.

"\n""\n"

The heart acts as a pump that circulates the blood forcing the blood through the vessels.

"\n""\n"

During each heartbeat, this force moves the blood from the maximum (systolic) pressure to the minimum (diastolic) pressure. The cardiac cycle is this complete series of events within each heartbeat. Blood pressure is measured in millimeters of mercury (mmHg).</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_2">Blood pressure is commonly expressed in terms of the systolic pressure over (/) the diastolic pressure, i.e. 120/80. The highest point of pressure in the heartbeat cycle is the systolic measurement—this is the exerted pressure when the heart contracts. The lowest point occurs between heartbeats and is the diastolic measurement—this is the minimum pressure in the arteries when the heart is at rest. </string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_3">The World Health Organization has established the following globally accepted guidelines for the assessment of blood pressure readings:"\n""\n"

Optimal blood pressure"\n"

"\t""\t"Systolic pressure &lt;120 mmHg"\n"

"\t""\t"Diastolic pressure &lt;80 mmHg"\n"

Normal blood pressure"\n"

"\t""\t"Systolic pressure 120~129 mmHg"\n"

"\t""\t"Diastolic pressure 80~84 mmHg"\n"

High-normal blood pressure"\n"

"\t""\t"Systolic pressure 130~139 mmHg"\n"

"\t""\t"Diastolic pressure 85~89 mmHg"\n"

Mild hypertension"\n"

"\t""\t"Systolic pressure 140~159 mmHg"\n"

"\t""\t"Diastolic pressure 90~99 mmHg"\n"

Moderate hypertension"\n"

"\t""\t"Systolic pressure 160~179 mmHg"\n"

"\t""\t"Diastolic pressure 100~109 mmHg"\n"

Severe hypertension"\n"

"\t""\t"Systolic pressure >179 mmHg"\n"

"\t""\t"Diastolic pressure >110 mmHg"\n""\n"



In the U.S., the blood pressure classifications from the 7th Report of the Joint National Committee on Prevention, Detection, Evaluation, and Treatment of High Blood Pressure are:



Normal blood pressure"\n"

"\t""\t"Systolic pressure &lt;120 mmHg"\n"

"\t""\t"Diastolic pressure &lt;80 mmHg"\n"

Prehypertension blood pressure"\n"

"\t""\t"Systolic pressure 120~139 mmHg"\n"

"\t""\t"Diastolic pressure 80~89 mmHg"\n"

Hypertension, Stage 1"\n"

"\t""\t"Systolic pressure 140~159 mmHg"\n"

"\t""\t"Diastolic pressure 90~99 mmHg"\n"

Hypertension, Stage 2"\n"

"\t""\t"Systolic pressure ≥160 mmHg"\n"

"\t""\t"Diastolic pressure ≥100 mmHg"\n""\n"



These categories are only a guideline; individual health status may vary based on age, gender, overall physical condition and heredity. Interpretation of individual measurements should be discussed and reviewed with a healthcare professional.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_4">High blood pressure, also known as hypertension, is a common condition in which the pressure exerted by the blood pushing against the blood vessels is high enough to potentially cause health problems, including heart disease. This condition is dangerous as it causes the heart to work harder to pump the blood through the body.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_5">Hypertension is often called ‘the silent killer’ because many people experience little or no symptoms. The name hypertension can be misleading as the prefix ‘hyper’ may seem to indicate hyperactive, tense or nervous behavior; in fact, seemingly a calm and relaxed individual may still suffer from high blood pressure or hypertension.

"\n""\n"

Home monitoring is a great way to help detect and monitor high blood pressure. Regular readings taken over a period of time can track the history of your results and indicate any changes, fluctuations or elevations in your blood pressure. An individual high reading is not necessarily an indication of hypertension or other health issue.

"\n""\n"

Only your healthcare provider should diagnose any medical condition. iHealth Blood Pressure Monitors provide a convenient way to test, track and share your results.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_6">If you are already diagnosed with high blood pressure, it is important to see your health care provider on a regular basis. The iHealth App is a convenient way to store, track and share your measurements with your healthcare provider so he or she can assist in treating your condition.

"\n""\n"

If you are not already diagnosed with high blood pressure but have concerns about the measurement results, it is suggested to see your healthcare provider for an accurate interpretation and diagnosis of your health.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_7">The guidelines set by the World Health Organization is a good place to start in interpreting blood pressure results. It is important to discuss with your healthcare provider what the ideal blood pressure is for your body type, lifestyle and overall health statBP by dateus.

"\n""\n"

Often, a blood pressure measurement can read as artificially elevated for a particular reading. It is important to follow the information provided in your Owner’s Manual and on the iHealth website (www.ihealthlabs.com) to properly prepare for the reading and for proper product use. If you feel your measurement is incorrect, wait several minutes and reattempt the measurement; try to remain calm and relaxed so as not to artificially inflate the results.

"\n""\n"

iHealth Blood Pressure Monitors also feature Irregular Heartbeat Detection. If an irregular heartbeat, or arrhythmia, is detected during the measurement, the Irregular Heartbeat icon will display on the results screen next to the pulse measurement. Consult with your healthcare provider regarding arrhythmia if this icon appears frequently.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_8">In order to ensure its accuracy, the iHealth Blood Pressure Monitors have obtained EC medical certification (Europe) as well as FDA approval (USA). They have been tested under the European and United States standards for non-invasive blood pressure monitors: AAMI SP10:2002 (Manual, electronic or automated sphygmomanometers) and EN1060–4:2004 (Non–invasive sphygmomanometers–Part 4: Test procedures to determine the overall system accuracy of automated non–invasive sphygmomanometers). These standards compare results of the iHealth devices with those of mercury manometers. The results are processed and analyzed in order to guarantee the medical reliability of the blood pressure monitors.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_9">There are no physical risks associated with taking your blood pressure at home with this product. If you find the measurements uncomfortable, consult with your healthcare professional regarding proper cuff application and tightness.

"\n""\n"

If you have vascular access (shunt) for kidney dialysis on your arm, do not check your blood pressure on that arm.

"\n""\n"

You can stop the measurement at any time during the measurement by sliding the STOP button to the right on the App screen to stop inflation.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_10">Yes. However, you will need to turn the function on before using offline measurement function.

        Sync your Monitor with with iHealth MyVitals App and go to “Set Up My devices” to turn the offline measurement function.

        To start measurements when disconnected from your mobile device (“offline”),

         turn on the Monitor by pressing the “START/STOP” button. Offline measurement is automatically enabled at your first online measurement. Offline measurement data will be uploaded to the device automatically upon the next

        synchronization between your mobile devices and Monitor.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_11">Yes. Click the “share” button and send data to any url such as a family member or doctor. You can also share data results on Facebook and Twitter or save it to other apps such as TargetWeight PRO.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_12">Once your personal profile is set up in the App, all your measurement data will upload to the Cloud automatically.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_13">No. Users need to select their own data to be saved to their personal account.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_14">The Wireless Blood Pressure Monitor is available in two different cuff sizes, which fit arm circumferences from 22 to 48 cm.

"\n""\n"

The Wireless Blood Pressure Wrist Monitor is available in one cuff size, which fits wrist circumferences from 13.5cm to 22cm.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_15">Sometimes it takes a few hours for data transmission. If your data cannot upload, please contact iHealth Customer Service.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_16">Make sure the cuff is applied to your bare arm, and press “START/STOP” to manually turn on the device.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_17">Hold the “START/STOP” button for 10 seconds to restore the Blood Pressure Monitor and restart the Android device. Updating the Android device to version 5.0 and above is recommended.

"\n""\n"

If the Bluetooth indicator light stays on for 2.5 seconds and off for 5 seconds, please press the “START/STOP” button for 10 seconds to restore. If the Bluetooth connection still cannot be established, the Bluetooth function might not work properly.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_18">The battery level might be too low. Try replacing the batteries.</string>
    <string name="bpfaq_content_19">The iHealth Blood Pressure Monitor Suite of Products is warranted to be free from defects in materials and workmanship appearing within one year from the date of purchase, when used in accordance with the instructions provided. The above warranties extend only to the original retail purchaser.

"\n""\n"

We will, at our option, repair or replace this product without charge covered by the above warranties. Repair or replacement is our only responsibility and your only remedy under the above warranties.

"\n""\n"

To obtain warranty service please contact Customer Service at 1-855-816-7705 or email support@ihealthlabs.com</string>

    <!-- act_faq_spo2 -->

    <string name="act_faq_spo2_title">Pulse Oximeter FAQ</string>
    <!-- SPO2 faq页面  question  -gbb -->

    <string name="Pulse_Oximeter_Setup">Pulse Oximeter Setup</string>
    <string name="pulse_oximeter_basics">Pulse Oximeter Basics</string>
    <string name="using_the_pluse_oximeter">Using the Pulse Oximeter</string>
    <string name="syncing_data">Syncing Data</string>
    <string name="troubleshooting">Troubleshooting</string>
    <string name="warranty_infornation">Warranty Information</string>

    <!-- ** Pulse Oximeter Basics ** -->

    <string name="faq_1" translatable="false">1.What is a Pulse Oximeter?</string>
    <string name="faq_2" translatable="false">2.What is oxygen saturation (SpO2)?</string>
    <string name="faq_3" translatable="false">3.What is the normal range for SpO2?</string>
    <string name="faq_4" translatable="false">4.What is the normal range for pulse rate?</string>
    <string name="faq_5" translatable="false">5.What is Perfusion Index?</string>
    <string name="faq_6" translatable="false">6.What kind of conditions may affect my reading?</string>
    <string name="faq_7" translatable="false">7.What are the factors influencing pulse rate?</string>
    <string name="faq_8" translatable="false">8.What is the measuring range and accuracy for iHealth Wireless Pulse Oximeter?</string>
    <string name="faq_9" translatable="false">9.When does the battery light indicator appear in the display?</string>

    <!-- ** Using the Pulse Oximeter  ** -->

    <string name="faq_10" translatable="false">1.How many measurements can be stored in the iHealth Wireless Pulse Oximeter?</string>
    <string name="faq_11" translatable="false">2.Does the App support multiple users?</string>
    <string name="faq_12" translatable="false">3.How many measurements can be stored in the App?</string>
    <string name="faq_13" translatable="false">4.Can I delete previous measurements on the App?</string>
    <string name="faq_14" translatable="false">5.Can I delete existing users on the App?</string>
    <string name="faq_15" translatable="false">6.Can measurements be taken without using an Android device?</string>

    <!-- ** Syncing Data  ** -->

    <string name="faq_16" translatable="false">1.Does the App recognize the offline measurement data of multiple users and sort the data automatically?</string>
    <string name="faq_17" translatable="false">2.How does data upload to my iHealth Cloud account?</string>

    <!-- ** Troubleshooting ** -->

    <string name="faq_18" translatable="false">1.What if my iHealth Wireless Pulse Oximeter does not turn on?</string>
    <string name="faq_19" translatable="false">2.What should I do if the Bluetooth connection failed?</string>
    <string name="faq_20" translatable="false">3.What should I do if my iHealth Wireless Pulse Oximeter doesn\'t show any results after performing the test?</string>

    <!-- ** Warranty Information ** -->

    <string name="faq_21" translatable="false">1.What are the terms and conditions of the warranty?</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_1" translatable="false">A pulse oximeter is a non-invasive device that quickly and easily measures your blood oxygen saturation (SpO2) level and pulse rate (heart rate).</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_2" translatable="false">Oxygen saturation is a measurement of how much oxygen the blood is carrying as a percentage of the maximum it could carry.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_3" formatted="false" translatable="false">For a regular healthy person, the normal SpO2 should be around 96% to 99%. However, altitude changes can affect a person\'s SpO2

         reading. When elevation is above sea level, the amount of oxygen in the air decreases. The higher the altitude is, the thinner the oxygen in the air is.

         For instance, a reading of 98% at sea level may decrease to 95% at 5,000 ft above sea level and further decrease to 90% at 10,000 ft. Consult your health

          professional for more information.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_4" formatted="false" translatable="false">The normal resting pulse rate is between 60 and 100 beats per minute. Consult your health professional for more information.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_5" formatted="false" translatable="false">Perfusion Index, or PI, is a relative assessment of the pulse strength at the monitoring site. PI ranges from .01%(very weak pulse strength) to 20%(very strong pulse strength).</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_6" translatable="false">Cold hands, weak pulse, hand movements, fingernail polish and acrylic nails are some of the most common factors that may affect a reading and cause inaccurate results.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_7" translatable="false">Many factors can influence pulse rate, including but not limited to physical activities, fitness level, emotional state, body weight, medications and body position.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_8" formatted="false" translatable="false">SpO2 measuring range: 70-99%.Average Root Mean Square (ARMS) of SpO2 accuracy: 80%∼99%: ±2%, 70%∼79%:±3%, 70%: no definition. "\n"

                                Pulse rate measuring range: 30-250bpm.Pulse rate accuracy: 30∼99bpm: ±2bpm, 100∼250bpm: ±2%.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_9" translatable="false">The battery light indicator appears when the battery is low.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_10" translatable="false">The iHealth Wireless Pulse Oximeter can store up to 100 measurements.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_11" translatable="false">Yes, the App supports multiple users, and each user has his or her own profile and data stored in the App.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_12" translatable="false">The App can store up to 9,999 measurements using the memory space of your Android device.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_13" translatable="false">Yes. To delete previous measurements, select “History” and then “Edit.” You may then delete any historical data one entry at a time.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_14" translatable="false">Yes. To delete an existing user, tap the user name at the top of the home screen, then select User Profile. Tap “Edit” and delete the user by tapping the “Delete User” button on the bottom.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_15" translatable="false">        Yes. Up to 100 measurements are automatically saved in the iHealth Wireless Pulse Oximeter when you measure offline. Offline measurement data will be uploaded to your Android device automatically upon the next connection.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_16" translatable="false">No. Users need to select their own data to be saved to their personal accounts.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_17" translatable="false">Once your personal profile is set up in the App, all your measurement data will be uploaded to the iHealth Cloud automatically.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_18" translatable="false">The battery may be low. Please charge the device using the included USB cable.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_19" translatable="false">Turn off and restart the iHealth Wireless Pulse Oximeter. Close and then relaunch the App. Updating your Android device to version 4.2.2 or above is required.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_20" translatable="false">Please make sure your finger is inserted correctly, as illustrated in the Quick Start Guide. With your finger in the correct position, keep perfectly still and test it again.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_21" translatable="false">The iHealth Wireless Pulse Oximeter is warranted to be free from defects in materials and workmanship appearing within one year from the date of purchase, when used in accordance with the instructions provided. The above warranties extend only to the original retail purchaser."\n"

                                 We will, at our option, repair or replace this product without charge covered by the above warranties. Repair or replacement is our only responsibility and your only remedy under the above warranties.</string>

    <!-- AM  Activity and Sleep Tracker FAQ   by gbb -->

    <string name="Activty_and_sleep_Setup">Activity and sleep Setup</string>
    <string name="general_information">General Information</string>
    <string name="information_and_setup">Information and Setup</string>
    <string name="syncing_your_iHealth_tracker">Syncing Your iHealth Tracker</string>
    <string name="information_about_activity_tracking">Information about Activity Tracking</string>
    <string name="information_about_sleep_tracking">Information about Sleep Tracking</string>
    <string name="charging_and_battery">Charging and Battery</string>
    <string name="trouble_shooting">Trouble Shooting</string>

    <!-- question -->


    <!-- General Information -->

    <string name="astfaq_1" translatable="false">1. What is the iHealth Activity and Sleep Tracker?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_2" translatable="false">2. What Android devices are the iHealth Tracker compatible?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_3" translatable="false">3. How does the iHealth Tracker work?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_4" translatable="false">4. What information does the iHealth Tracker display?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_5" translatable="false">5. How should I wear my iHealth Tracker?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_6" translatable="false">6. What materials are used in the manufacture of the iHealth Tracker?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_7" translatable="false">7. Is the iHealth Tracker waterproof?</string>

    <!-- ****Information about Setup -->

    <string name="astfaq_8" translatable="false">1. How do I set up my iHealth Tracker on my Android device?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_9" translatable="false">2. Why do I need to “link” the Tracker to my iHealth MyVitals account?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_10" translatable="false">3. Can I link the iHealth Tracker to multiple accounts?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_11" translatable="false">4. What if I want to give my Tracker to someone else?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_12" translatable="false">5. Why should I update my Android App?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_13" translatable="false">6. When does my iHealth Tracker reset？And what happens to the previous data?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_14" translatable="false">7. Does the iHealth Tracker have PC connectivity?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_15" translatable="false">8. How do I turn on airplane mode?</string>

    <!-- ****Syncing your iHealth Tracker -->

    <string name="astfaq_16" translatable="false">1. How does the iHealth Tracker sync with the iHealth MyVitals App?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_17" translatable="false">2. How often should I sync Tracker data with my Android device?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_18" translatable="false">3. Does the Tracker need to be near the Android device for syncing?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_19" translatable="false">4. How do I sync the time on the Tracker display when changing time zones?</string>

    <!-- ****Information about Activity Tracking -->

    <string name="astfaq_20" translatable="false">1. How does calorie tracking work?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_21" translatable="false">2. Is the iHealth Tracker suitable for all physical activities?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_22" translatable="false">3. Can I log my non-walking or non-running activities?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_23" translatable="false">4. Will my calories burned be counted twice if I manually log the activity?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_24" translatable="false">5. How does the Idle Alarm work and how do I set it up?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_25" translatable="false">6. How does the Activity Level feature work?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_26" translatable="false">7. Can I wear the iHealth Tracker while performing rigorous activities such as basketball, soccer and other team sports?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_27" translatable="false">8. Does the iHealth Tracker detect steps while traveling by car or when sitting?</string>

    <!-- ****Information about Sleep Tracking -->

    <string name="astfaq_28" translatable="false">1. How do I turn on the sleep tracking feature?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_29" translatable="false">2. How does sleep tracking work?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_30" translatable="false">3. Can the Tracker save my sleep data if I forgot to turn on the sleep mode?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_31" translatable="false">4. What are "awaken times"?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_32" translatable="false">5. How does the silent alarm work, and how do I set it up?</string>

    <!-- ****Charging and Battery -->

    <string name="astfaq_33" translatable="false">1. Can I check the battery level on the iHealth Tracker?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_34" translatable="false">2. How long does the battery last on a full charge?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_35" translatable="false">3. How do I charge the battery, and how long does it take?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_36" translatable="false">4. What do I do if the battery is completely drained?</string>

    <!-- ****Trouble Shooting -->

    <string name="astfaq_37" translatable="false">1. How do I get iHealth Tracker firmware updates?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_38" translatable="false">2. How does Factory Reset work?</string>
    <string name="astfaq_39" translatable="false">3. When do I need to reset the iHealth Tracker and how do I do that?</string>

    <!-- content -->

    <string name="astfaq_content_1" translatable="false">The iHealth Wireless Activity and Sleep Tracker (the iHealth Tracker) tracks every step you take, distance traveled, calories burned, and sleep efficiency. Its silent alarm feature wakes you up gently without disturbing the person next to you, and the smart alarm feature helps you remember to be more active. A playful Activity Level feature motivates you to be more active for different levels of steps achieved. It connects with an Android device via Bluetooth 4.0.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_2" translatable="false">-  Samsung Galaxy S4 4.2.2 ONLY currently due to Samsung\'s change of Bluetooth protocols in 4.3 \n

        -  Nexus 4(4.3+) \n

        -  Nexus 5(4.3+) \n

        -  HTC ONE(4.3+)</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_3" translatable="false">The iHealth Tracker is optimized for walking, running, and everyday lifestyle activities. It gives you an idea of how active you are, in general, by tracking total activity throughout the day and calories burned from your activities. It also tracks your sleep patterns and helps you get a closer look at your sleep efficiency over time.

"\n""\n"

The iHealth Tracker works with the free iHealth MyVitals app, which has personalized health tools to help you get the most out of your data and better manage your health goals.

 "\n""\n"

The iHealth Tracker uses a 3-axis accelerometer that detects your motion patterns in three dimensions and converts that information to your steps taken, calories burned, distance travelled, and sleep efficiency. </string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_4" translatable="false">The iHealth Tracker shows time of day, number of steps taken, distance traveled, calories burned, and daily activity level. Press the button to switch between each view.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_5" translatable="false">The iHealth Tracker can be worn one of two ways: on your wrist, or on your waist with the clip provided. When wearing on your waist, always use the clip provided, as the clip will trigger the Tracker to switch from “wrist tracking” to “waist tracking” for maximum tracking accuracy.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_6" translatable="false">The wristband accompanying the iHealth Tracker is made of hypoallergenic TPU rubber, which is latex- and PVC-free and is safe to use next to your skin.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_7" translatable="false">It is water proof, you can wear it when rain, splash, sweat and swim, even take shower, but water temperature can not be more than 30 degrees.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_8" translatable="false">Setup is quick and easy. Please follow the steps below to set up your iHealth Tracker:

"\n""\n"

•Download the iHealth MyVitals app from the Google Play.\n

•In “Settings” turn the Bluetooth feature “On”.\n

•Open the App and follow the onscreen instructions to set up and personalize the Tracker.

 "\n""\n"

For detailed information, please refer to the Quick Start Guide included in the product packaging, or download it from iHealthlabs.com. </string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_9" translatable="false">To protect your personal data, the iHealth tracker links the Tracker with your iHealth MyVitals account during your first setup process. The linking feature ensures that only you can sync the Tracker with your Android device, even if you misplace the Tracker.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_10" translatable="false">​You can only have one Tracker linked to one iHealth MyVitals account at a time.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_11" translatable="false">If you decide to give the Tracker to someone else, you will first need to do a factory reset to restore original factory settings and unlink the tracker from your iHealth MyVitals account. Please refer to the “How does Factory Reset work” question and answer in the “Trouble Shooting ” section, below.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_12" translatable="false">A newer version App will contain more features and improvements. Update your Android App for higher performance and bug fixes.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_13" translatable="false">Your Tracker will reset each night at midnight, and all of your data will reset to zero. Your minute-to-minute data will be stored in your Tracker for up to 14 days without syncing. Daily syncing is recommended.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_14" translatable="false">Currently, the iHealth Tracker has android and Android connectivity.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_15" translatable="false">Turn on the airplane mode in the App. An airplane icon will appear on your Tracker display. Press and hold the button for 2 seconds to turn it off. Please note that data syncing is not possible while your Android device is in airplane mode.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_16" translatable="false">To sync data from your iHealth Tracker to the App, you must have an active Internet connection and Bluetooth must be turned on. You should see the Bluetooth icon (on the upper-right corner of your Android device screen, next to the battery level) flash a few seconds, and then stay lit up. This indicates that your iHealth Tracker and Android device are connected.

"\n""\n"

To sync the iHealth Tracker, simply open the App and tap on the “Activity” Card to enter the Activity main page. Your tracker should initiate a sync automatically from there. Alternatively, you can use the “Sync” button on the same page to force a syncing.

"\n""\n"

If your Android device is connected to the internet, your data will be uploaded to the iHealth Cloud as well (if you have a cloud account).</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_17" translatable="false">A daily sync is recommended but not required. The iHealth Tracker can record detailed data for up to 14 days between each sync. Daily syncing only takes a few minutes; however, the more data stored, the longer it may take to sync.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_18" translatable="false">During syncing, keep the Tracker within 16 feet of your Android device.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_19" translatable="false">When you travel to a different time zone, the iHealth Tracker will automatically update its time when you sync the Tracker with your Android device.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_20" translatable="false">The iHealth Tracker records calories burned from your activities throughout the day, and your Basal Metabolic Rate (BMR), which is the amount of calories burned while at rest (in other words, the energy expended to sustain your regular body functions while you sleep). This calculation is based on your age, gender, height and weight. The Tracker displays the total calories you have burned since midnight each day.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_21" translatable="false">The iHealth Tracker works best when the wrist is moving as part of the overall movement, and your foot makes contact with the ground, such as when walking or running. The iHealth Tracker is less suited for tracking resistance exercises such as weight lifting and yoga. Though it will capture data if worn during these activities, these types of motions might not be recorded as accurately as running or walking.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_22" translatable="false">You can manually log resistance exercise activities in the “My Diary” section of the iHealth MyVitals App. This allows for more accurate estimates of calories burned to be included in your daily totals.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_23" translatable="false">Let’s say you wear the iHealth Tracker during 30 minutes of basketball, and you log the activity in the App to find out the number of calories burned during basketball play, the App will make the adjustment and count only the calories from the activity you logged manually.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_24" translatable="false">You can set up the Idle Alarm in the iHealth MyVitals App. The iHealth Tracker will vibrate gently for approximately 4 seconds to remind you to get up and be more active.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_25" translatable="false">To help you stay motivated, the iHealth Tracker rewards you at different levels of activity achievement, as indicated by a playful leaping frog who can move to 3rd, 2nd, and 1st place, respectively. This is how it works:

"\n""\n"

At 2,500 steps: The leaping frog jumps to 3rd place; "\n"

At 5,000 steps: The leaping frog jumps to 2nd place;"\n"

At 10,000 steps: The leaping frog jumps into 1st place and is crowned.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_26" translatable="false">It is safe to wear the iHealth Tracker during these rigorous activities, and it will record your step count from these movements. However, the calorie count may not accurately reflect the intensity level of activity performed. For the most accurate amount of calories burned, we recommend that you manually enter all non-walking and non-running activities type in the App.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_27" translatable="false">The iHealth Tracker is designed to ensure that false steps are not recorded while traveling by car or when sitting. However, when there is a constant motion detected by the sensor, it might pick up some steps. Road conditions and hours spent on the road could also affect tracking. For instance, you might see some steps when you are driving in bumpy traffic or during a longer commute. If you plan to drive a long distance, just remove the tracker during your trip so it won’t track while driving.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_28" translatable="false">To start tracking your sleep, press the button for 2 seconds until “sleep” appears in tracker display. When you awake, press the button for another 2 seconds to end sleep recording and to resume activity tracking. Open the App to sync and view your sleep data.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_29" translatable="false">When you wear the iHealth Tracker on your wrist at bedtime and enable its “Sleep” mode, it will detect and analyze your motion patterns throughout the night, and turn these data into useful information, such as how long it took you to fall asleep, the number of times you woke up throughout the night, and how long you were actually asleep versus merely lying in bed.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_30" translatable="false">No, you must enable sleep mode for the Tracker to record your sleep data.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_31" translatable="false">The iHealth Tracker detects your body movements while you are asleep, such as tossing and turning, then converts that data into Awaken Times. Knowing your total Awaken Times can help you better understand the quality of rest that you are getting.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_32" translatable="false">Silent alarms can be set up in the App. Silent alarms wake you gently—and without disturbing your partner—by vibrating softly for a duration of 40 seconds.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_33" translatable="false">The iHealth Tracker’s battery level appears on the tracker display and in the App. When the battery level reaches 20%, the Tracker will vibrate to remind you to recharge it.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_34" translatable="false">The iHealth Tracker is powered by a rechargeable built–in battery. The battery typically lasts at 5–7 days between charges. If you check stats frequently or set up multiple alarms, you may need to charge battery more often.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_35" translatable="false">Plug one end of the charging cable into the USB port on the back of the Tracker, and the other end into your computer’s USB port. It should take about two hours for the tracker to fully charge from an empty battery.

"\n""\n"

You can charge it more frequently for shorter amounts of time to ensure that the battery never empties completely.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_36" translatable="false">The battery will drain completely if you forget to charge the battery as recommended, or if it is not used for a lengthy period of time. When this happens, recharge the battery and launch the App to sync the iHealth Tracker with your Android device before using the Tracker again.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_37" translatable="false">We are constantly looking for ways to improve your iHealth Tracker experience. From time to time, we update the device firmware to enhance product performance. When a firmware update is released, a notification message will pop up in the App. Follow the onscreen instructions to complete the update.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_38" translatable="false">Your iHealth Tracker is for your personal use only, and it is linked to your iHealth MyVitals account when you first set up the Tracker. If you want to give the Tracker to a family member or friend, you will need to restore its original factory settings before passing it on. To do so, go to Settings > Device Settings in the iHealth MyVitals App.

"\n""\n"

Factory Reset erases all your personal data from the Tracker, including any asynchronous data. Please be sure to sync the Tracker by opening the App before performing a Factory Reset. You will not lose previously synced data in the App and the cloud.</string>
    <string name="astfaq_content_39" translatable="false">If you are experiencing Bluetooth connection difficulties or unusual behavior on the iHealth Tracker display, you can perform a basic reset on the tracker to reboot it. Resetting the Tracker will not affect your settings, such as alarms.

"\n""\n"

To reset your iHealth Tracker, press and hold the button for 5 seconds until the word “resetting” appears. Continue to hold the button for another 3 seconds until you see the clock display.</string>

    <!-- act_faq_scale -->

    <string name="act_faq_scale_title">Scale FAQ</string>

    <!-- AM  Scale FAQ   by gbb -->

    <string name="body_weight_knowledge">Body Weight Knowledge</string>
    <string name="before_use">Before Use</string>
    <string name="use_and_tips">Use and Tips</string>
    <string name="data_syncing">Data Syncing</string>
    <string name="warranty">Warranty</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_body_weight_knowledge" translatable="false">BODY WEIGHT KNOWLEDGE</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_before_use" translatable="false">BEFORE USE</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_use_and_tips" translatable="false">USE AND TIPS</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_data_syncing" translatable="false">DATA SYNCING</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_warranty" translatable="false">WARRANTY</string>

    <!-- question -->


    <!-- Body Weight Knowledge -->

    <string name="scalefaq_1" translatable="false">1. What is body composition?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_2" translatable="false">2. What is body fat percentage?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_3" translatable="false">3. What is bone mass?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_4" translatable="false">4. What is muscle mass?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_5" translatable="false">5. What is body water percentage?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_6" translatable="false">6. What is visceral fat?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_7" translatable="false">7. What is visceral fat rating?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_8" translatable="false">8. What is Daily Calorie Intake (DCI)?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_9" translatable="false">9. How do calories affect body weight?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_10" translatable="false">10. How do sports and activities affect body weight?</string>

    <!-- ****Before Use -->

    <string name="scalefaq_11" translatable="false">1. What types of batteries are needed?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_12" translatable="false">2. Can the measurement units be changed?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_13" translatable="false">3. How is does the Wi-Fi connection work?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_14" translatable="false">4. Can the Scale be used on any surface?</string>

    <!-- ****Use and Tips -->

    <string name="scalefaq_15" translatable="false">1. Can I wear shoes or socks when taking measurements?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_16" translatable="false">2. Is holding the Android device necessary when taking a weight measurement?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_17" translatable="false">3. Can I use the Scale without an Android device?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_18" translatable="false">4. Do measurements take up memory in my Android device?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_19" translatable="false">5. There are fluctuations in the measurements. Why is this happening?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_20" translatable="false">6. Within what distance does the Android device have to be from the Scale in order to function properly?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_21" translatable="false">7. Can I use the Wireless Body Analysis Scale without an Android device?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_22" translatable="false">8. If there is no Android device, how is a user selected? </string>
    <string name="scalefaq_23" translatable="false">9. Can several people use the same Wireless Body Analysis Scale?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_24" translatable="false">10. Can I use the scale if I have a pacemaker?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_25" translatable="false">11. Does the Scale work even when the Wi-Fi network is off?</string>

    <!-- ****Data Syncing -->

    <string name="scalefaq_26" translatable="false">1. Can I share my data? </string>
    <string name="scalefaq_27" translatable="false">2. How are results uploaded to the iHealth Cloud website?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_28" translatable="false">3. The Scale’s model name is not listed on the “Bluetooth” Menu of the Android device.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_29" translatable="false">4. The Bluetooth connection failed.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_30" translatable="false">5. The Wi-Fi sharing pop-up window doesn’t show on the Android device.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_31" translatable="false">6. The Wi-Fi symbol doesn’t appear on the Scale display.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_32" translatable="false">7. The App and Scale connection failed.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_33" translatable="false">8. The Wi-Fi symbol turns off after flashing and the Scale displays “ER 4”.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_34" translatable="false">9. The Scale does not respond.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_35" translatable="false">10. The Scale displays “Lo”.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_36" translatable="false">11. The Scale displays “ER 0”, “ER3”, “ER6”, “ER7” or “ER8”.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_37" translatable="false">12. The Scale displays “ER 1”.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_38" translatable="false">13. The Scale displays “ER 2”.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_39" translatable="false">14. The Scale displays “ER 5”</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_40" translatable="false">15. The Scale displays “----”.</string>

    <!-- ****Warranty -->

    <string name="scalefaq_41" translatable="false">1. What are the terms and conditions of warranty?</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_42" translatable="false">2.</string>

    <!-- content -->

    <string name="scalefaq_content_1" translatable="false">In physical fitness, body composition is used to describe the percentages of fat, bone and muscle in human bodies. Because muscular tissue takes up less space in our body than fat tissue, our body composition, as well as our weight, determines leanness. Two people of equal height and body weight may look completely different from each other because they have a different body composition.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_2" translatable="false">Body fat percentage is the amount of body fat as a proportion of your body weight. Reducing excess levels of body fat has shown to reduce the risk of certain conditions such as high blood pressure, heart disease, diabetes and cancer.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_3" translatable="false">Bone mass is the amount of bone (bone mineral level, calcium or other minerals) in the body. Research has shown that exercise and the development of muscle tissue are related to stronger, healthier bones.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_4" translatable="false">Muscle mass is the weight of muscle in your body. The muscle mass displayed includes the skeletal muscles, smooth muscles (such as cardiac and digestive muscles) and the water contained in these muscles. Muscles play an important role as they act as an engine in consuming energy. As your muscle mass increases, your energy consumption increases helping you reduce excess body fat levels and lose weight in a healthy way.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_5" translatable="false">Body water percentage is the total amount of fluid in a person’s body expressed as a percentage of their total weight. Water plays a vital role in many of the body’s processes and is found in every cell, tissue and organ. Maintaining a healthy total body water percentage will ensure the body functions efficiently and will reduce the risk of developing associated health problems. See healthy ranges below:"\n""\n"

        "\t""\t"Female: 45 - 60%"\n"

        "\t""\t"Male: 50 - 65%</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_6" translatable="false">Visceral fat is also known as abdominal fat, organ fat or intra-abdominal fat. It is located inside the abdominal cavity, packed in between organs such as the stomach, liver,intestines, or kidneys. Visceral fat is different from subcutaneous fat underneath the skin and intramuscular fat interspersed in skeletal muscles. Fat in the lower body, as in thighs and buttocks, is subcutaneous, whereas fat in the abdomen is mostly visceral."\n""\n"

         Visceral fat is likely to cause visceral fat syndrome or other lifestyle-related diseases. Men or post-menopausal women are more prone to accumulation of visceral fat.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_7" translatable="false">Visceral fat is the fat that is in the internal abdominal cavity, surrounding the vital organs in the trunk (abdominal) area. Research shows that even if your weight and body fat remains constant, as you get older the distribution of fat changes and is more likely to shift to the trunk area especially post menopause."\n""\n"

        Rating from 1 to 12: Indicates you have a healthy level of visceral fat. Continue monitoring your rating to ensure that it stays within the healthy range."\n""\n"

        Rating from 13-59: Indicates you have an excess level of visceral fat. Consider making changes in your lifestyle possibly through diet or exercise."\n"</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_8" translatable="false">Daily Calorie Intake (DCI) is the sum of calories for basal metabolism, daily activity metabolism (activities including daily household chores), and diet-induced thermogenesis (energy used in connection with digestion, absorption, metabolism, and other eating activities). It is an estimate of how many calories you can consume within the next 24  hours to maintain your current weight.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_9" translatable="false">Losing 1 pound requires that you burn approximately 3,500 more calories than you consume."\n""\n"



Your estimated daily calorie budget is the number of calories you should consume in order to create the deficit required to achieve your goal. It is computed using two factors:"\n""\n"

"\t""\t"An estimate of the number of calories you burn each day"\n"

"\t""\t"The number of pounds you are attempting to lose per week"\n"

For example, if you are attempting to lose one pound per week and you normally burn 2,500 calories per day, your daily calorie budget would be 2,000. This number is computed as follows:"\n""\n"

"\t""\t" Weekly calorie deficit required to lose one pound = 3,500"\n"

"\t""\t"Daily calorie deficit = 500 (3,500 divided by 7)"\n"

"\t""\t"Daily calorie budget = 2,000 (2,500 minus daily calorie deficit of 500)"\n""\n"

The reliability of this method is contingent upon an accurate estimate of your daily calories burned. The estimate may therefore be inaccurate for a variety of reasons (e.g. more or less active metabolism than normal or more or less daily occupational activity than normal).</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_10" translatable="false">The number of calories you burn each day at rest is estimated using a standard formula based on height, weight, age, and gender (the Mifflin equation). This equation produces what is known as a resting metabolic rate (RMR)."\n""\n"

         Your daily calories burned are estimated by multiplying your RMR by your Personal Activity Level (PAL). Your PAL is assumed to be sedentary to light (e.g. a typical office worker). In more technical terms this corresponds to a PAL of 1.45. This PAL corresponds to the following set of daily activities:"\n""\n"

    "\t""\t"Sleeping - 8 hours"\n"

    "\t""\t"Personal care (dressing, showering) - 1 hour"\n"

"\t""\t"Eating - 1 hour"\n"

"\t""\t"- 1 hour"\n"

"\t""\t"Sitting (office work, selling produce, tending shop) - 8 hours"\n"

"\t""\t"Driving car to/from work - 1 hour"\n"

"\t""\t"General household work - 1 hour"\n"

"\t""\t"Light leisure activities (watching TV, talking) - 3 hours"\n""\n"

The Mifflin equation provides a good approximation of RMR for most people, however, individual metabolisms vary. If you feel that your RMR varies from that of the typical person (e.g. because a doctor or nutritionist has more accurately measured your RMR) you may wish to adjust your daily calorie budget accordingly. You can do this using the Adjustment field of the Daily Calorie Budget screen.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_11" translatable="false">The Wireless Body Analysis Scale requires four 1.5V AA batteries which are included in the package.  Rechargeable batteries may not suitable for this product.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_12" translatable="false">Yes. The units of measurement can be changed. Choose from pounds (lbs), kilograms (kg), or stone (st) by moving the switch located on the bottom of the Scale under the battery cover.

        "\n""\n"

         You may also change the units of measurement on the app display.  Click on the information icon (i) and select “Units” on the Information Page.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_13" translatable="false">Please download the Quick Start Guide from www.ihealthlabs.com.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_14" translatable="false">In order to get the most accurate readings, we recommend against placing the Scale on an uneven floor, soft surface, or carpet while weighing. Keeping the Scale on a hard, flat surface is recommended.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_15" translatable="false">The Scale can get weight data if you wear shoes or socks, however, if you want to get all 9 body composition data points, it is necessary to step on the four electrodes with bare feet.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_16" translatable="false">No. It is not necessary to hold the Android device. As long as the Android device is within range and it is successfully connected to the Scale via Bluetooth.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_17" translatable="false">Yes. The Scale can be used without an Android device after the first connection is established. The Scale will transfer the data to the iHealth Cloud.

        "\n""\n"

         If there is no internet available, it may be necessary to synch the Android device at least once every 200 measurements. New measurements overwrite older ones stored in the Scale.

         "\n""\n"

         The App will automatically synch with the iHealth Cloud every time it is launched.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_18" translatable="false">Yes. The measurements along with a date and time stamp are stored in the memory of your Android device; however, the data only takes the space of an MP3 file.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_19" translatable="false">Be sure your bare feet cover all four electrodes or the results may not be accurate.

        "\n""\n"

         Every time the Scale is moved it may need to be initialized and auto-calibrated. Initializing the Scale resets the internal parts allowing the Scale to find the correct “zero” weight and ensure accurate readings. To initialize the scale:

         "\n""\n"

        "\t""\t"Place the Scale on a hard, flat surface."\n"

     "\t""\t"With one foot, press the platform of the Scale so that numbers appear on the display and remove your foot."\n"

    "\t""\t" Wait a few seconds."\n"

     "\t""\t"The Scale is now re-calibrated.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_20" translatable="false">In a normal environment (without high electromagnetic interference), the Android device and the Scale can be used within 65 feet/20 meters of the wireless router.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_21" translatable="false">Yes. The Scale can be used without an Android device after the first connection is established. It may be necessary to synch your device at least once every 200 weigh-ins as new measurements overwrite older ones stored in the Scale. When the Wi-Fi connection is re-established, measurement data will be uploaded to your Android device.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_22" translatable="false">The Scale can automatically identify the user when the user\'s physical characteristics are distinctly different. When the user\'s physical characteristics are similar, the user needs to confirm the current user.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_23" translatable="false">The Scale can accommodate up to 20 users if an Android device is not used."\n""\n"

         If you use the Scale with an Android device, the number of users is unlimited. Used in this way, the Scale is an ideal tool for families as well as Fitness Clubs and Sports Teams.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_24" translatable="false">NO. People with pacemakers are strongly advised NOT TO USE the Scale.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_25" translatable="false">Yes, you can continue to weigh-in as usual. The Scale can save up to 200 weight measurements. It will upload them to your App as soon as the connection is restored.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_26" translatable="false">Yes. Simply click the “share” button and your data can be emailed to any URL you designate such as a family member or doctor. You can even share your results on popular socialnetworking sites like Facebook and Twitter or save it to other Apps such as TargetWeight PRO.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_27" translatable="false">Once a personal profile is set up in the App, all the measurement data will upload to the Cloud automatically.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_28" translatable="false">Make sure the Scale is on “Set” status by pressing the “Set” button on the back of the Scale.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_29" translatable="false">Turn off and on the Bluetooth button on the Bluetooth Menu (see SettingsGeneralBluetooth) and re-establish the Bluetooth connection."\n""\n"

         If the problem persists, restart your Android device.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_30" translatable="false">Re-establish the Bluetooth connection.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_31" translatable="false">Make sure the Android device is connected to a router. "\n""\n"

         Make sure the MAC address is not filtered by a router."\n""\n"

         Repeat beginning from Step 3 of “Connect Scale to An Internet Router” in the Quick Start Guide.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_32" translatable="false">Make sure the Scale is powered on, and the Wi-Fi symbol is stable (not flashing)."\n""\n"

         Make sure the Android device and Scale is connected to the same router.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_33" translatable="false">Make sure your router is powered on and the router settings such as “password” and “name” have not been changed.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_34" translatable="false">Remove the batteries from the Scale. Wait one minute and re-install the batteries. If the problem persists, replace with a new set of batteries.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_35" translatable="false">Make sure the batteries are installed correctly. If the problem persists, replace with a new set of batteries.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_36" translatable="false">Remove the batteries, wait one minute and replace with a new set of batteries. If the problem persists, please contact iHealth Customer Service.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_37" translatable="false">The current weight may be beyond the measurement range of 330 lbs or 150 kg.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_38" translatable="false">Place feet in the center of the Scale, stand still, and allow the Scale to turn off completely after weighing. Do not move the Scale unnecessarily.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_39" translatable="false">The current weight is unsteady. Retake your measurement and be sure to stand still on all four electrodes with bare feet.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_40" translatable="false">The Scale failed to detect body impedance. Make sure all four electrodes are stood on with bare feet and try again.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_41" translatable="false">The Wireless Body Analysis Scale is warranted to be free from defects in materials and workmanship within one year from the date of purchase when used in accordance with the provided instructions.  The warranty extends only to the end user."\n""\n"

         We will, at our option, repair or replace without charge any Scale covered by the warranty.  Repair or replacement is our only responsibility and your only remedy under the warranty.</string>
    <string name="scalefaq_content_42" translatable="false">42.</string>
</resources>